Poris To

sw130nam@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/poristo/

Profile

Graduated from the Hong Kong Design Institute with passions in UI/UX design, I dedicated to developing my career in the industry.

Over the 5 years of solid experience on the website, mobile app, and system interface designs, I work closely with developers and clients to maintain high-quality works on different aspects, including web-based applications, eCommerce websites, payment dashboards, and mobile apps.

With his positive learning attitude, supportive assistant, and adaptability in this fast-changing tech-based design industry, he successfully earned the trust and satisfaction from colleagues and different clients.

Experience

FGUSI

Assistant Design Manager Jan 2019 - Aug 2020

- Design UI/UX for Website, Mobile Apps, and Web-bases systems
- Identify opportunities to improve overall website performance
- Document project information
- Oversee and secure project development schedule

Senior Multimedia Designer Mar 2018 - Dec 2018

- Create hi-fi interactive prototypes to accurately demonstrate the app to clients.
- Provide quality control checks (visual) for client deliverables
- Conducted layout adjustments based on data gathered during usability testing
- Recommending alternative design solutions based on technical limitations, the ability for quick problem-solving earned positive feedback from stakeholders

As One Interactive Limited

Senior Frontend Developer June 2017 - Mar 2018

- Work closely with the design team to quickly iterate new features
- Apply javascript animation in high demand and the design user flow and interface
- Perform mentoring and host internal training for colleagues, ensure best coding practices applied
- Improve the critical path of rending and perform other Web-performance improving techniques

Web Designer Sep 2014 - June 2017

- Participate across a wide range of digital projects from the conceptual phase to the design and development phase
- Support social media marketing team by creating engaging digital design
- Provide design concept for campaigns' pages
- Design and develop multiple WordPress sites in an integrated responsive layout

Education

Creative Media Design Hong Kong Design Institute 2011 - 2014

Languages

Cantonese - Fluent

Mandarin - Professional

English - Conversationable

Skills

Design

Wireframing
Prototyping
UX Research
Interactive Mockups
Usability Testing
System Thinking
Photography

Development

HTML/CSS jQuery Wordpress Styled-Components High Fidelity Mockup

Tools

Abstract Sketch Adobe CC Invision Principle Zeplin Marvelapp